<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tom Plant's blog</title><link>https://tplant.com.au/</link><description>Recent content on Tom Plant's blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tplant.com.au/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Winja CTF 2021</title><link>https://tplant.com.au/blog/winja-ctf-2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tplant.com.au/blog/winja-ctf-2021/</guid><description>A hack quest CTF by nullcon, good variety of difficulty and categories. Keeping track of the map interface was painful though.
Are Yaar Points: 120 In a village there were 4 best friends one of them was Ramlal whose favorite dish was &amp;lsquo;pulihora&amp;rsquo;. He was a farmer and with lot of hardwork and passion he became CEO of a Software Organization. https://twitter.com/kulkarniramlal
The Twitter account linked to a GitHub profile, containing a single repo.</description></item><item><title>Kubernetes on a Budget</title><link>https://tplant.com.au/blog/k8s-on-a-budget/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tplant.com.au/blog/k8s-on-a-budget/</guid><description>Prologue PaaS webapps are cool and all, but sometimes ya boi needs to deploy something legacy (🤮). Time to build some infra over the midsem break.
Zoomer gotta zoom so I obviously want to use containers. And overengineering for high availability sounds fun. All the cool kids are using this thing called kubernetes, surely that&amp;rsquo;s perfect for little old me, right? googles hosted kubernetes pricing oh shit go back [meme bullying k8s]</description></item><item><title>Microsoft Teams as an LMS</title><link>https://tplant.com.au/blog/teams-lms/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tplant.com.au/blog/teams-lms/</guid><description>Prologue With Queensland adopting the ATAR assessment system, digital assessment storage was one of many new requirements to tackle. We were lagging behind other schools with no existing LMS, but this was a blessing in disguise - we weren’t locked into a non-compliant vendor.
Time was running out, so Microsoft Teams was chosen to become a short-term repository/learning management system. Nothing is cheaper than free (so I was told), and the SharePoint backend would be easy to migrate if/when needed.</description></item></channel></rss>